伟大的发明
AMAZlNG DlSCOVERlES
欢迎各位收看 “伟大的发明”！
Welcome,everybody! Welcome to Amazing Discoveries!
又播出了！
It's on again!
我们能不能别看了啊？
Guys,could we please not watch this?
你是否遇过这种情形？ 你正打算倒一杯牛奶…
This ever happen to you? You go to get a glass of milk...
但你左思右想 却怎么也打不开纸盒
...but these cartons are so flinging,flanging hard to open!
天啊，你说对了，麦克
Boy,you said it,Mike.
一定有个好办法 的确有，凯文
- There's gotta be a better way. - There is,Kevin!
可不可以别看了？ 不行，凯文
-Can we please turn this off? -No way,Kevin!
如果我告诉你有个新产品 能保证…
What if I told you there's a new product that guarantees...
你再也不用费力 打开牛奶纸盒呢？
... you'll never have to open up milk cartons again?
看看这个牛奶大师2000！
Meet the Milkmaster 2000!
挑起你的兴趣了吧 是啊，挑得我心痒痒的
-lntrigued? -You're flinging,flanging right I am!
这是他第一次使用 你就知道有多容易了
This is the first time he's used this. You'll see how easy this is to do.
任何牛奶纸盒都适用 真简单！
-This works in any milk carton. -Wow,it is easy!
这样我就可以每天喝牛奶了
Now I can have milk every day.
我看不下去了
l can't watch this anymore.
你已经受了折磨了，我们换台吧
You've suffered enough.We'll change it.
-这样的状况发生过多少次了？-肯定有更好的办法的！
-How many times has this happened?-There's gotta be a better way!
本集播出： “隐喻性的隧道”
The One With the Metaphorical Tunnel
真的没有好看的电影
It's official. There are no good movies.
那就去看难看的电影 然后在那里亲热
So let's go to a bad one,and make out.
或许你希望我转过去 你们可以像兔子一样在我背上跳着玩？
Perhaps you'd like me to turn so you can bunny-bump against my back?
老兄，怎么了？ 或许该由你来告诉我吧
-Hey,man. What's up? -Maybe you can tell me.
我的经纪人问我 为何今天的试镜没有出现
My agent wants to know why I didn't show up at my audition today...
这几周来第一个好机会 你怎么没转告我？
... my first good one in weeks. How could you not give me the message?
告诉你，我虽然喜欢罪恶感…
I'll tell you,I do enjoy guilt...
但这次不是我
... but it wasn't me.
是的，就是他！
Yes,it was. It was him!
好吧，是我啦
Okay,it was me!
怎么会是你？ 一切真是疯狂啊，你知道吗？
-How was it you? -Well,it was all so crazy,you know?
钱德躲在衣橱里，倒数十秒…
Chandler was in the closet,counting to 10...
已经数到七了 我一直找不到地方躲
...and I hadn't found a place to hide yet.
我一直想告诉你，我写在手上 你看，全都在这儿
I meant to tell you,and I wrote it all down on my hand. See? All of it.
是啊，就是我的试镜
Yep,that's my audition.
看吧，这就是为何 我到处都要放便条纸
See? Now,this is why I keep notepads everywhere.
对，这就是为何 我们都不邀你一起玩
Yep. And that's why we don't invite you to play.
这样有什么悲剧的？ 再约一次时间啊
What is the great tragedy here? Get yourself another appointment.
艾斯黛试过了，选角导演说 我已经错过了机会
Estelle tried. The casting director told her I missed my chance.
这样太不公平了！
Well,that is unfair!
我来打给她 我告诉她都是我的错
I'll call her. I'll tell her it was my fault.
不，选角导演不可能 跟演员的朋友谈
You can't. The casting director doesn't talk to friends.
她只跟经纪人谈 她的生活层面真狭隘啊
-She only talks to agents. -What a sad little life she must lead.
你在干嘛？ 我知道啦…
-What are you doing? -No,I know,I know.
我是菲比布菲公司的凯特琳
Hi,this is Caitlin from Phoebe Buffay's office.
菲比可以和安谈一谈吗？
Is Anne there for Phoebe?
她自己明白是什么事
She'll know what it's about.
挂掉，快挂掉…
Hang up. Hang up right
安妮，你好 乔伊崔比亚尼有点小问题
Annie? Hi. Listen,we've got a problem with Joey Tribbiani.
很显然地，他错过了试镜 你是转告我们公司的哪一位？
Apparently,he missed his audition. Who did you speak to in my office?
艾斯黛？ 我真不知该拿她怎么办
Estelle? I don't know what to do with her.
就算丈夫离开，并放火烧房子 世界依旧照常运作
So your husband leaves and burns down the apartment. The world doesn't stop.
还有其他人受到惊吓吗？
Is anybody else scared?
若乔伊错失这次试镜 那是艾斯黛的错，我不管！
If Joey loses this audition,then that is it for Estelle. I don't care!
安妮，你真善良 你何时能见他？我需要笔！
Annie,you are a doll. What time can you see him? I need a pen. Pen!
快给这个女人一本便条纸 给她便条纸，快点！
Get the woman a pad! Get the woman a pad! A pad! A pad!
现在你就需要便条纸啦
Oh,now you want a pad.
真有趣，丑陋裸男光着身子，他的狗却穿着毛衣
That's funny. Ugly Naked Guy's naked,but his dog's wearing a sweater.
我的小男孩呢？
Where's my boy?
我的小男孩在这儿
Here's my boy!
还有他的芭比娃娃！
And here's his Barbie!
我儿子干嘛玩芭比娃娃？
What's my boy doing with a Barbie?
他自己在玩具店选的 他很喜欢呢
He picked it out at the store. He loves it.
他去哪儿都带着它 就像能给他安全感的小毯子
He carries it everywhere,like a security blanket.
这个却穿着雪靴 和时髦的贝雷帽
But with ski boots and a kicky beret.
是啊，很可爱
Yeah,it's cute.
再说一次 他为何要玩这个东西？
Why does he have it again?
他有个洋娃娃，那又怎样？
So he's got a doll. So what?
除非你怕他将来 长大后变成…
Unless you're afraid he's gonna grow up to be...
演艺圈的人
...in show business.
这件事跟他…
This wouldn't have to do with the fact...
被两个女人扶养长大 有没有关系？
...that he's being raised by two women?
好，若你能接受他喜欢芭比 那我也可以
You know what? It's fine. If you're okay with the Barbie thing,so am l.
把芭比给爸爸，芭比给我
Give Daddy the Barbie. Give me the Barbie.
你要不要玩怪兽车？
Don't you wanna play with a monster truck?
不要？好吧
No? Okay.
那要不要恐龙士兵？
How about a Dino-Soldier?
罗斯，你真可悲
You are so pathetic.
为何不让你的儿子玩芭比？
Why can't your son just play with his doll?
我要去上班了
I gotta go to work.
有人看到我左边的胸部吗？
Has anybody seen my left boob?
我喜欢那部电影（《我的左脚My Left Foot》）
I loved that movie.
在这里，你在干嘛？
Here it is. What are you doing?
对不起，这样很舒服
I'm sorry. It just felt nice.
去接电话
Answer the phone.
我只有一只手，你应该帮我的 帮我拿件毛衣来
I only got one arm. You should do stuff for me. Get me a sweater.
快点接啦！是珍妮丝
Just do it! It's Janice.
如果我接了 我今晚就得跟她见面
And if I get it,I'll have to see her tonight.
那太好了 我今晚得跟她见面
That's great. I'll have to see her tonight.
你为何不想见她？
Why don't you want to see Janice?
昨晚我们在吃晚餐 当餐点送来时…
Last night at dinner,when the meals came...
她把一半烤鸡肉放到我盘里 拿走我所有的番茄
...she put half her chicken piccata on my plate and took all my tomatoes.
这样很不好是因为…
And that's bad...
你不喜欢烤鸡肉吗？
...because you hate chicken piccata?
你不想与人分享你的番茄 番茄对你很重要
You didn't want to share your tomatoes. Tomatoes are very important to you.
突然间，我们就是“情侣”了
Suddenly,we were this "couple."
然后我脑袋里的警报开始大响
And this alarm started going off in my head.
“为了你的人生，快跑！ 快离开这栋大楼！”
"Run for your life! Get out of the building!"
男人真是令人难以置信，珍妮丝想着给你鸡肉
Men are unbelievable.Janice thought she was giving you chicken.
她并没想给你吓人的鸡肉
She didn't think she was giving you scary chicken.
你们这些人是怎么回事？
What is it with you people?
心中一旦产生感情 就要马上逃开？
The minute you feel something,you have to run away?
我知道，那就是…
I know. That
就是我今晚不想去的原因 我怕自己说出一些蠢话
That's why I don't want to go tonight. I'm afraid I'll say something stupid.
你是说男人那一套 故意冷漠，保持距离…
You mean that "guy thing" where you act mean and distant...
直到我们提出分手？
... until we break up with you?
你们都知道啊？
You know about that?
我能怎么做？ 我想度过这个阶段
What do I do? I wanna get past this.
我不想再害怕承诺
I don't want to be afraid of commitment.
就像跃过一个隧道 到达另一端！
I want to go through the tunnel to the other side!
就是不再害怕承诺
Where there's no fear of commitment.
我们有没有…
Do we have any
有没有任何想法？
Do we have any thoughts here?
我没度过那种隧道啦 因为…
I've never been through the tunnel myself because...
过隧道的规定是 你车里不能多于一个女生
...you're not allowed through with more than one girl in the car.
但我看来，跟其他事差不多 你得面对恐惧
But it seems to me it's pretty much like anything else. Face your fear.
你怕高的话，就到大楼顶端
Fear of heights? Go to the top of the building.
你怕虫的话…
You're afraid of bugs.
就逮一只
Get a bug.
你的情况是，你害怕承诺…
You have a fear of commitment.
你就到那里去 做一个最勇于承诺的男人
So I say you go in there and you be the most committed guy there ever was!
令人讶异的是，很有道理呢
Amazingly,that makes sense.
你这么觉得？ 是啊，快去吧，老兄！
-Do you think? -Oh,yeah! Go for it,man!
从高处跳下水！
Jump off the high dive!
用目光击退枪枝！ 在风中撒尿！
Stare down the barrel of the gun! Pee into the wind!
若我得用目光击退枪枝…
If I'm staring down the barrel of a gun...
我大概已经尿得到处都是了
...I'm gonna be pretty much peeing every which way.
“中央公园”
CENTRAL PERK
听听这个然后告诉我你们的想法
Listen to this and tell me what you think.
很有趣
That's interesting.
-亲爱的？ -哦，是因为这个传呼机
-Honey?-Oh, because it's a beeper.
是你今天早上的试镜！
It's your audition from this morning!
可以借用电话吗？
Can I use the phone?
当然，这是紧急事件 以及冒牌经纪人专用
Sure,that's what it's there for. Emergencies and pretend agents.
快啊，宝贝
Come on,baby! Come on!
菲比布菲要回覆呼叫
Hi. I have Phoebe Buffay returning a page.
好，她在车上 我帮你接过去
Okay,she's in her car. I'll have to patch you through.
演得很好
Very nice touch.
好，请说吧
Okay,go ahead.
快说话…
Talk,talk,talk!
安妮，你好
Hi,Annie?
太好了，你成功了！
Fantastic. You got it!
你问我他愿意突破尺度吗？ 我也不知道
Will he work for scale,you ask me? Well,I don't know about that.
除非我知道，而且他也愿意
Except that I do and he will.
太好了，你人真好
Great. Oh,you are such a sweetheart.
我很愿意与你共进午餐！
I would love to have lunch with you!
不如就下个…
How about we have lunch next
正经过隧道
Went through a tunnel.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
太感谢你了
Oh,thank you so much!
真有趣，我从未用过汽车电话
It was really fun. I mean,I've never talked on a car phone before.
你真了不起 你能不能帮我个大忙？
You are so amazing! Could you do me this huge favor?
还有一个试镜，我很想参加 但艾斯黛无法帮我搞定
There's another audition I want,and Estelle couldn't get me in.
我不知道，一次还很好玩…
I don't know. It was fun one time,but
拜托，再一次就好了
Please? It would just be this one more.
其实是两次啦
Well,actually it's two.
两次？
Two?
好啦，其实是三次
Well,really it's three.
拜托，你这么厉害 我爱你
Please? You're so good at it. I love you.
好，就这三次了，好吗？
Okay. But just these three,right?
不，是四次
No,it's four.
你今天怎么会想在家吃？
So how come you wanted to eat in tonight?
因为我想…
Because I wanted...
送你这个东西
...to give you this.
你这只小狗狗
Are you a puppy!
接触印相纸！
Contact paper!
一个跟你上床的人送你…
What do you say when someone you're sleeping with...
接触印相纸，该说什么？
...gives you contact paper?
还有呢，你看跟它搭配的…
Wait,there's more. See,the contact paper is to go...
就是你的新抽屉！
...in your brand new drawer!
看，其实这个抽屉 正好与我的梳妆台搭配
See,the drawer actually goes in my dresser.
你不用这么做啊
You didn't have to do this.
对，我要这么做
Yes,I did.
是的，我要这么做 因为你是我的女朋友
Yes,I did. Because you're my girlfriend...
而女朋友就该得到这些
...and that's what girlfriends should get.
我得买个元音了…
Well,I gotta buy a vowel...
因为…哦我的天啊（oh与元音“o”同音）
... because,oh,my God!
谁会想的到，有一天…
Who would've thought that someday...
钱德宾会买个抽屉给我？
... Chandler Bing would buy me a drawer?
我可想不到
Well,not me.
但事实就是这样 而且还不只如此
But that's what's happened. And there's more.
我们应该去旅行
We should take a trip.
我们该这么做？
We should?
我们是情侣，情侣就该这样
We're a couple,and that's what couples do.
我还要去见你爸妈
And I wanna meet your parents.
我们应该跟你爸妈一起去旅行
We should take a trip with your parents!
我想不用了 因为你已快把我搞迷糊了（与“旅行”同词）
I don't think we need to because you're tripping me out right now!
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我很好
No,I am.
我真的很好 真是太不可思议了
I actually am! This is amazing.
我一生都在害怕这个时刻
My entire life,I have feared this place.
但现在时候到了 我却觉得没什么大不了
And now that I'm here,it's like,what was the big deal?
我可能会说“我们同居吧” 却还是若无其事
I could probably say,"Let's move in together," and I'd be okay.
你可能想跟我一起住？
You probably want us to move in together?
我竟不会因此而害怕 是啊，但我会害怕！
-lt doesn't scare me! -Yeah,well it scares me!
我根本还没离婚！ 你只是邀我来吃意大利面…
I'm not even divorced yet! You just invited me over here for pasta...
而现在你就在说 要住在一起的事…
...and now you're talking about moving in together.
我其实还不太饿
And I wasn't even that hungry.
你知道吗？时间有点晚了 我最好先…
You know what? It's getting really late,and I should just
别走，我吓着你了！ 我说太多了！
Don't go! I've scared you! I've said too much!
对于爱情，我是无药可救 笨拙却又充满渴望
I'm hopeless and awkward and desperate for love!
珍妮丝，是我
Hey,Janice,it's me.
我只是想在到街上追你前 先跟你道歉
I wanted to apologize in advance for having chased you down the street.
拿去吧，甜心 应该有帮助的
Here you go,honey. This will help.
我追上她，然后她说…
So I catch up to her and she says...
这段感情发展太快 我们得放慢脚步
...this relationship's going too fast and we have to slow down.
这样绝不是好现象
That is never good.
于是我就变得…
Then I got all...
很空虚又很黏人
... needy and clingy.
-你没乞求她吧？-我说“请”了
-You didn't beg, did you?-l said please.
你说“请”的时候 中间的E有没有拖长音？
Was it please with one E in the middle or lots of E's?
哦上帝啊，我乞求她了
Oh, dear Lord, l begged.
等等，或许不算太糟 你们怎么结束的？
Wait a minute. Maybe it's not so bad. How did you leave it?
她说她会再打给我
She said she'd call me.
天啊
Oh,God.
恭喜你来到我们这一边的隧道
Welcome to our side of the tunnel.
对了，这个冰淇淋味道好烂
This ice cream tastes like crap,by the way.
因为这是低卡无乳脂 豆浆制的假冰淇淋
Well,it's that low-cal-nondairy-soymilk junk.
我们把真正的留到 实在无法挽留了才吃
We save the real stuff for the truly terminal cases.
若你一直被搞得一团糟 你就要换成低脂的
When you're getting screwed over all the time,you gotta switch to low fat.
没错，你得这么做
Yeah,you do.
你不认为我已无法挽留了？
You don't think I'm terminal?
不尽然，你并非无法挽留 我们只要防止事情恶化
Not at all. You're not terminal. We just need some damage control.
好，我该打电话给她吗？ 不
Okay. Should I call her? -No
这段时间很重要，一旦你发现 自己的手又伸向电话…
It's a critical time. If you feel yourself reaching for that phone...
你就去购物 或者给你的屁股洗个泡泡浴
...go shopping,get your butt in a bubble bath.
若你希望她回来 你就得开始表现冷漠
If you want her back,you have got to start acting aloof.
冷漠？
aloof？
她必须知道 你并不空虚
She has to know you're not needy.
所以你要做的就是…
So what you have to do is...
假装不经意地碰到她…
...you have to accidentally run into her on purpose...
然后表现得很冷漠
...and then act aloof.
-然后就会很顺利？ -我想是这样的
-And then l'll be okay?-Yeah. l think so.
这样我就不会失去她了？
So I'm not gonna lose her?
甜心，你不是个失败者啊（与“失去她”谐音）
Oh,honey,you're not a total loser.
我是说 “我就不会失去她了？”
I said,"So I'm not gonna lose her?"
看看谁来了！
Guess who's here!
是玩具王国里 最勇敢的人，班！
It's the toughest guy in Toyland,Ben!
真正的美国英雄 我是大兵乔（又译“特种部队”）！
Real American hero I'm G.I. Joe!
把芭比娃娃放下…
Drop the Barbie. Drop the Barbie.
大兵乔？
G.I. Joe?
你真的觉得他会 喜欢那玩意儿？
You really think he'll fall for that?
大兵乔？
G.I. Joe?
好棒，我可以玩吗？
Cool! Can I play?
班，你看，这个玩具 保护了美国海外油股！
Look,Ben! It's a toy that protects U.S. oil interests overseas!
加油，乔！
Go,Joe!
菲比，你在这儿啊 不，我不是，抱歉
-There you are! -No,it's not. Sorry.
菲比，等等…
But,Phoebe,wait,wait. Phoebe!
乔伊啊，我刚没认出你来…
Oh,Joey! Oh,okay! See,I didn't recognize you...
因为你穿着这条裤子
...in those pants.
我参加试镜的电视电影有任何回音吗？
That TV movie I went in for,did you hear anything?
我想我应该很有机会的
I think I got a shot at it.
对，他们打来了 你没有入选
Yes,they called! You didn't get it!
好吗？我是说你落选了 对不起…
Okay? I mean,you didn't get it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没关系 这种事本来就会发生
That's okay. These things happen.
但是不应该发生，你知道吗？
But they shouldn't happen. You know what?
你进的这一行 真的好可怕
You're in a terrible,terrible business.
我不想成为 那个让你难过的人
I don't want to be the person who makes you look like that.
我没事的，你看
I'm okay. See?
你看起来很难过并且毛骨悚然
Now you're sad and creepy.
我很抱歉，我要辞职
I'm sorry. I quit.
不，你不能辞职！ 你是我遇过最好的经纪人
No,no,you can't quit! You're the best agent I ever had.
当一个演员本来就会被拒绝 你不能过于自责
Rejection is part of being an actor. You can't take it personal.
他们说没遇过一个意大利演员 有这么怪的意大利腔
They said they'd never met an ltalian actor with a worse ltalian accent.
他们真的这么说？
They actually said that?
天啊，又是那种表情 你看，我不能做这个工作
Oh,God,there's that face again. See? I can't do this job!
这就是为何你得做这份工作
This is why you have to do this job!
经纪人都得说谎
Agents always lie.
艾斯黛总是说 “他们要另一种方式”
Estelle just says stuff like,"They went another way."
但是这一点嘛，我可以改进
But this? I can use this.
我可以学一种新的腔调
I can work on a new accent.
好，若对你有帮助，那就好了
Yeah,okay. If it helps you,okay. Yeah.
你抓不到我，乔！
You'll never get me,Joe!
不用了，谢谢
No,thank you.
-钱德？-你好，珍妮丝
-Chandler？ -Hello，Janice
你在这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
只是买买东西而已
Just a bit of shopping.
你还好吗？
How have you been?
你在装英国腔吗？
Are you being British?
再也不会了
Not anymore.
你怎么在这里买东西？ 你又不住在这一带
Why are you shopping here? You don't live in this neighborhood.
你是不是在这里等我？
Were you here waiting for me?
我只是…
I'm just...
要买一点派对用的东西
... picking up some things for a party.
大麦？
Barley?
什么样的派对会供应大麦？
What kind of party serves barley?
很抱歉，我的朋友 不像你朋友那么有水准
I'm sorry if my friends aren't as sophisticated as yours.
派对在哪里举行？
Where is this party?
就在切尔西
Here in Chelsea.
是谁的派对
Whose party is it?
一个女人
A woman's.
哪个女人？
What woman?
切尔西
Chelsea.
或者你是背着我跟别人约会…
Either you're seeing somebody behind my back...
然后成了世界第一混蛋…
...which would make you the world's biggest jerk...
或者就是你假装跟别人约会…
...or you're pretending to see somebody...
让你成为最可悲的人 我会立刻在此为你哭泣
...which makes you so pathetic I could cry right here!
这两种男人，你想当哪一种？
So which of these two guys do you want to be?
我可以当那个人吗？
Can I be that guy?
我们收到很多善意的拒绝 有很多地方要改进
Okay,we got some more good rejections. Lots of stuff to work on.
好，说吧
Okay. Shoot.
好，那个动物园广告
Okay. Oh,the zoo commercial.
我没得到那个角色？
I didn't get it?
他们说你简直不像个人类
They said that you "weren't believable as a human being."
所以你可以针对这一点改进
So you can work on that.
很好
Great.
还有呢？
What else?
那些非百老汇戏剧界的人 说你好看可是很笨
The off-Broadway-play people said that you were "pretty but dumb."
等等，对不起 他们是说你好笨
Oh,no wait. I'm sorry. That's "pretty dumb."
看，没关系啊 不…是真的
Look,it's okay,no,no,no. Really.
听着…
Look...
我很感谢你…
... I really appreciate this...
但我还是回去找艾斯黛好了
... but I'm gonna have to go back to Estelle.
别误会 你当经纪人当得比她好…
Don't get me wrong. You're a better agent than she is...
至少我跟着她 我这非常笨的脑袋还保得住
... but at least with her,I don't want to blow my pretty dumb brains out.
是的，不，我能了解
Yeah,no,I understand.
你可以吗？谢谢你
You do? Thanks. Okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你是不是故意编这些出来 就不用当我的经纪人了？
Did you make all that stuff up to get out of being my agent?
被你发现了
Oh,he caught me.
我真失败！
I am so busted!
我就是这么怀疑的
That's what I suspected!
然后我只好…
And then I just,you know...
把一袋大麦丢到她身上 然后逃出那间店
...threw the bag of barley at her and ran out of the store.
天啊，我们叫你表现冷漠 不是像个笨蛋
My God,Chandler,we said be "aloof," not "a doof."
我这次真的搞砸了，对吧？
I've actually ruined this,haven't l?
这次可以吃 真正的冰淇淋了吗？
Is it time for the good ice cream now?
-是时候了 -没错，可以了
-It's time -Yeah,it is.
你知道吗？一切都没问题的 知道为什么吗
You know what? Everything's gonna be okay.You know why？
因为这样你就可以增肥65克了
Because you got 65 grams of fat coming your way.
珍妮丝，你可以等一下吗？
Can you hold on for a second?
好，我该怎么办？
What do I do?
我不知道，这是史无前例的
I don't know. This is unprecedented.
若我们做出像你一样的事 男人绝不会再打来了
If we did what you did,a man would never call.
我知道了，假装你刚睡醒 这样就可以摆脱她了
I got it! Pretend you just woke up. That'll throw her off!
睡意惺忪！ 对，脾气暴躁！
-Be sleepy! -Yes! And grumpy!
你们怎么…？ 别开始数小矮人的名字（《白雪公主》的小矮人的名字）
What are you? Stop naming dwarfs!
我很高兴你打来
I'm so glad that you called.
我知道我最近的表现很怪…
I know I've been acting really weird lately...
那是因为我太爱你了
...and it's just because I'm crazy about you...
我就变得很蠢，又很害怕…
...and I just got stupid and scared...
然后就变得非常笨
...and stupid a couple more times.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
真的？
Really?
他真幸运，若珍妮丝是男的…
He's so lucky. If Janice were a guy...
她现在已经跟别人上床了
...she'd be sleeping with somebody else by now.
我也爱你
I love you too.
真是太不公平了！
It's so unfair!
大兵乔…？
G. I. Joe? G. I. Joe?!
我不知如何告诉你们 但他真的选了这个玩具
I don't know what to tell you guys. That's the doll he chose.
你怎么做的？ 把玩具沾糖吗？
What'd you do,dip it in sugar?
听着，大兵乔获胜 芭比娃娃出局了
Look,G. I. Joe's in,Barbie's out.
如果你们不能接受 那你们就太糟糕了
And if you guys can't deal with it,that's just your too bad.
你干嘛这么小家子气 他有个芭比，有什么大不了？
What are you being such a weenie for? So he has a Barbie. Big deal.
你以前都打扮得像女生
You used to dress up like a woman.
什么？
What?
你以前都穿妈的衣服啊
The way you used to dress up in Mom's clothes?
你在说什么啊？
What are you talking about?
宽帽子、珍珠、粉红小手提包
The big hat,the pearls,the little pink handbag?
好，这些都是你编出来的
Okay. You are totally making this up.
你怎么可能不记得？
How can you not remember?
你还要我们叫你“碧”啊
You made us call you "Bea"?
天啊
Oh,God.
我真的从没这么快乐过
I've literally never been this happy.
不是还有一首歌吗？
Wasn't there a little song?
拜托，老天，来一首歌吧
Oh,please,God,let there be a song.
根本没有什么歌…
There was no song. There was no song.
我是碧
I am Bea
我喝茶 够了！
-I drink tea -That's enough.
你要不要…
Won't you....
你要不要在我身旁跳舞？
Won't you dance around with me?
我是碧
I am Bea
我喝茶
I drink tea
你要不要在我身旁跳舞…
Won't you dance around with?
罗斯？
Ross?